Ciaran Marriott

07928 969410 marriott2004@me.com https://cmarriott1.github.io/

Profile

I've been interested and involved in computer science for nine years ever since I first joined a coding club at school. I've always been fascinated with how code functions. The process of assembling code together as a whole and seeing the fruits of my labour is an immensely satisfying process to me. I've grown familiar with multiple languages and have enjoyed the associated challenge with taking up and completing projects. I'm excited to further expand my knowledge with programming as well as developing my interpersonal skills further amongst a team.

Key skills and certifications

Languages: C++, C#, Python, SQL, assembly

Game engines: Unity, Unreal Engine.

Collaborative software: GitHub, Notion, Flack, Trello, Teams, Zoom

Other: Visual Studio, Photoshop, Object Oriented Programming, SFML, Pygame

Education

• Sheffield Hallam University, MComp (Hons) Computer Science for Games

- Achieved a first (81%) in my Programming 2D Games module which involved me making 2D game projects under varying circumstances. I made some games on my own and others with a group of other students. I made some using game engines but I also made one using just a C++ library.
- Achieved a first (81%) in my Focus on Computer Architecture module which has taught me fundamental things about computers such as the intricacies of the hardware and understanding assembly language.
- Achieved a first (82%) in my Mathematics for Graphics module. This taught me relevant information that could be applied to my game development.

Tapton School

 A-levels, Sept 2020 - June 2022: Computer Science (B), Mathematics (A), Further Mathematics (C),

Work History

Volunteering at Age UK (July 2023 - Present)

- Managed the order and positioning of stock on the shop floor with customer habits in mind
- Recorded statistics such as number of items donate and how much new stock has been put out on a given day.

Programmer for Wdangcan Creations (July 2023 - Present)

- Experienced working as a programmer with a larger scale team of around 15 other people.
- Familiarised myself with a streamlined workflow underneath a game development company.

Interests and Hobbies

Esports - Competed in fighting game tournaments. Consistently improved my skills over the span of a couple years in a supportive competitive environment.

Languages - Doing a Duolingo course on Japanese. Have amassed a streak beyond 100 days, attaining basic knowledge of the language.